(Sheldon:)Oh, I've been meaning
to tell you,
(Sheldon:)I figured out
your magic trick.
(Howard:)Really?
(Leonard:)Oh, yes.
(Sheldon:)In fact, I improved upon it.
(Howard:)I'd love to see that.
(Howard:)How about you, Raj?
Beefaroni and a show?
(Raj:)How do you turn that down?
All right. (clears throat)
(Sheldon:)Pick a card.
(Priya:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)Bippity-boppity-boo.
(beeps)
(Howard:)What's with the wand
and the beep?
(Sheldon:)The wand is called showmanship,
(Sheldon:)and the beep is none
of your business.
(text alert tone sounds)
(Sheldon:)Oh! Excuse me.
(Sheldon:)I'm getting a text message
(Sheldon:)completely unrelated
to this magic trick.
(Sheldon:)Oh, look, my
dry cleaning's ready.
(Sheldon:)And your card was
the five of spades. Ta-da.